One of them put an end to the marriage, until the other came back for revenge.
Buried Alive is a thriller, crime, horror film directed by Frank Darabont.
A married woman and her lover plot to kill her husband
to make off with the insurance money.
However, their attempt to murder him using poisonous
fish toxins backfires in surprising ways.
Clint Goodman, played by Tim Matheson.
Joanna Goodman, played by Jennifer Jason Leigh.
Cort van Owen, played by William Atherton.
Sheriff Sam Eberly, played by Hoyt Axton.
Quintan, played by Jay Gerber.
Bill Scorby, played by Wayne Grace.
Buried Alive is a 1990 American made-for-television horror thriller film directed by Frank Darabont
and starring Tim Matheson, Jennifer Jason Leigh, William Atherton and Hoyt Axton.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, while the
scenario, dark humor, and ending received some praise.
It has often been overlooked in Darabont's directorial
catalogue due to the success of his later films.
The film explores themes of poison, coffin, revenge,
love affair, extramarital affair.
The tone is dark and intense.